[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "How are you going to make yourself sexy on the national stage?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "make", "yourself", "sexy", "on", "the", "national", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "You know, I'm not about making myself sexy on the national stage.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "about", "making", "myself", "sexy", "on", "the", "national", "stage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 58, "question": "What do you make of your rivals, Mr. Perry in particular, given he's the latest frontrunner?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "your", "rivals", ",", "Mr.", "Perry", "in", "particular", ",", "given", "he", "'s", "the", "latest", "frontrunner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Oh, I think -- you know, again, I go back to my child story that I analogize on my campaign, \"The Little Engine That Could.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "--", "you", "know", ",", "again", ",", "I", "go", "back", "to", "my", "child", "story", "that", "I", "analogize", "on", "my", "campaign", ",", "``", "The", "Little", "Engine", "That", "Could", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Perry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "How do you explain the American public to back a little engine when clearly what the American economy needs is a bloody great steam train?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "explain", "the", "American", "public", "to", "back", "a", "little", "engine", "when", "clearly", "what", "the", "American", "economy", "needs", "is", "a", "bloody", "great", "steam", "train", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "RB", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "NN", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "How much more tax would you like Warren Buffett to pay?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "more", "tax", "would", "you", "like", "Warren", "Buffett", "to", "pay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, Warren Buffett, as you know, pays capital gains taxes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Warren", "Buffett", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "pays", "capital", "gains", "taxes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "If I'm watching this as ordinary Joe on the street, I'm thinking, well, I would say why isn't Warren Buffett paying income tax and what are you going to do about it to make sure the super rich like him do pay income tax?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "'m", "watching", "this", "as", "ordinary", "Joe", "on", "the", "street", ",", "I", "'m", "thinking", ",", "well", ",", "I", "would", "say", "why", "is", "n't", "Warren", "Buffett", "paying", "income", "tax", "and", "what", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "about", "it", "to", "make", "sure", "the", "super", "rich", "like", "him", "do", "pay", "income", "tax", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Pardon?", "question_tokens": ["Pardon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I said stop him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "stop", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Why are you laughing?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "laughing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "He doesn't collect income tax.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "n't", "collect", "income", "tax", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "What do you mean by that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "mean", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Well, you know, a lot has been written about this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "lot", "has", "been", "written", "about", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Do you think homosexuality is a sin?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "homosexuality", "is", "a", "sin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Well, that's a decision not for a politician.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "decision", "not", "for", "a", "politician", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "How many sons do you have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "sons", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "We have four boys and three girls.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "four", "boys", "and", "three", "girls", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "How would you feel if one of your sons turned around one day and said, \"Dad, I'm gay\"?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "feel", "if", "one", "of", "your", "sons", "turned", "around", "one", "day", "and", "said", ",", "``", "Dad", ",", "I", "'m", "gay", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "''", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "I would embrace them, love them and try to help them through what I would see as a very difficult and troubling time in their lives.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "embrace", "them", ",", "love", "them", "and", "try", "to", "help", "them", "through", "what", "I", "would", "see", "as", "a", "very", "difficult", "and", "troubling", "time", "in", "their", "lives", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "I have to say that your views you espoused on this issue are bordering on bigotry, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "say", "that", "your", "views", "you", "espoused", "on", "this", "issue", "are", "bordering", "on", "bigotry", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Could you tell me?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "tell", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele"]}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "What do you make of her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "I think Michele is a dynamic person -- someone who can certainly get out there and rally the crowd and has taken some pretty strong stances on issues.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Michele", "is", "a", "dynamic", "person", "--", "someone", "who", "can", "certainly", "get", "out", "there", "and", "rally", "the", "crowd", "and", "has", "taken", "some", "pretty", "strong", "stances", "on", "issues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "In other words, is that the dream ticket for the GOP really?", "question_tokens": ["In", "other", "words", ",", "is", "that", "the", "dream", "ticket", "for", "the", "GOP", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Well, I can't speak for anybody else.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "speak", "for", "anybody", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Kerrey"]}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Your thoughts?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "thoughts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "That was Bob Kerrey who said it as a joke and apologized not only to me, but told the reporter that it was said in jest.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "Bob", "Kerrey", "who", "said", "it", "as", "a", "joke", "and", "apologized", "not", "only", "to", "me", ",", "but", "told", "the", "reporter", "that", "it", "was", "said", "in", "jest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Have you ever had your moments?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "had", "your", "moments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, gosh, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "gosh", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Have you ever broken the law, senator?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "broken", "the", "law", ",", "senator", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "Well, yeah, I admitted back when I was running for the Senate that when I was in college that I smoked pot, and that was something that I did when I was in college.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yeah", ",", "I", "admitted", "back", "when", "I", "was", "running", "for", "the", "Senate", "that", "when", "I", "was", "in", "college", "that", "I", "smoked", "pot", ",", "and", "that", "was", "something", "that", "I", "did", "when", "I", "was", "in", "college", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "No other skeletons you want to get of your chest while you're here?", "question_tokens": ["No", "other", "skeletons", "you", "want", "to", "get", "of", "your", "chest", "while", "you", "'re", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "I know you're a Catholic, so I'm not in the confessional.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "you", "'re", "a", "Catholic", ",", "so", "I", "'m", "not", "in", "the", "confessional", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Victor"]}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "In reality, what is it you look for in a guy who you think can become a guy who can beat Floyd Mayweather, one of the great boxers in the world?", "question_tokens": ["In", "reality", ",", "what", "is", "it", "you", "look", "for", "in", "a", "guy", "who", "you", "think", "can", "become", "a", "guy", "who", "can", "beat", "Floyd", "Mayweather", ",", "one", "of", "the", "great", "boxers", "in", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "E LA HOYA: It's odd, because obviously Victor can touch on this in depth.", "answer_tokens": ["E", "LA", "HOYA", ":", "It", "'s", "odd", ",", "because", "obviously", "Victor", "can", "touch", "on", "this", "in", "depth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Floyd Mayweather"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Do you get that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "I get that quite a bit.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "get", "that", "quite", "a", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "What happens?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I just tap them on the shoulder, like hey, dude, my bad.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "tap", "them", "on", "the", "shoulder", ",", "like", "hey", ",", "dude", ",", "my", "bad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "What is the signal that means if you progress with this, there is going to be terrible pain heading your way?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "signal", "that", "means", "if", "you", "progress", "with", "this", ",", "there", "is", "going", "to", "be", "terrible", "pain", "heading", "your", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I make no eye contact.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "make", "no", "eye", "contact", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Do you get it, Oscar?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "it", ",", "Oscar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Let me tell you the story.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "tell", "you", "the", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Your father did too?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "father", "did", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "He walked out four years later.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "walked", "out", "four", "years", "later", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Once you became famous, did either of your parents make any attempt to contact you?", "question_tokens": ["Once", "you", "became", "famous", ",", "did", "either", "of", "your", "parents", "make", "any", "attempt", "to", "contact", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "I actually went out of my way to find both of my parents.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "went", "out", "of", "my", "way", "to", "find", "both", "of", "my", "parents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Did he know what had happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "know", "what", "had", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kansas"]}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Where did you find him?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "find", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "I went back to Kansas and I asked around everywhere.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "went", "back", "to", "Kansas", "and", "I", "asked", "around", "everywhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "What's your advice when a guy like Victor comes to you and says he wants to do that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "advice", "when", "a", "guy", "like", "Victor", "comes", "to", "you", "and", "says", "he", "wants", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "I told him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "told", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Victor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Did he have an answer or not really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "have", "an", "answer", "or", "not", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "I actually ended up not even asking him why.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "ended", "up", "not", "even", "asking", "him", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "POS", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "But he couldn't listen to me 100 percent because I'm not his dad, you know?", "question_tokens": ["But", "he", "could", "n't", "listen", "to", "me", "100", "percent", "because", "I", "'m", "not", "his", "dad", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "ORGAN: Let's just turn to the fight for a moment.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Let", "'s", "just", "turn", "to", "the", "fight", "for", "a", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "How do you think the balance lies right now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "the", "balance", "lies", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I'm not really sure how the balance lies.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "really", "sure", "how", "the", "balance", "lies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Does fear enter your thinking at all?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "fear", "enter", "your", "thinking", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "What kind of man is he to fight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "man", "is", "he", "to", "fight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "First of all, like you said, he is a great fighter.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "like", "you", "said", ",", "he", "is", "a", "great", "fighter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "How good is this guy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "good", "is", "this", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "He's very good.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Did you hit him properly?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "hit", "him", "properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "He was going to beat me up.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "going", "to", "beat", "me", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Victor"]}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "POS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "If you actually got in the ring, who would win?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "actually", "got", "in", "the", "ring", ",", "who", "would", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Let me put it this way, if I was at my prime and Victor's at his prime, it will be one hell of a fight.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "put", "it", "this", "way", ",", "if", "I", "was", "at", "my", "prime", "and", "Victor", "'s", "at", "his", "prime", ",", "it", "will", "be", "one", "hell", "of", "a", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I had to take the upper hand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "to", "take", "the", "upper", "hand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Do you wish you'd had a figure like yourself, perhaps, to help you along the way, to navigate that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wish", "you", "'d", "had", "a", "figure", "like", "yourself", ",", "perhaps", ",", "to", "help", "you", "along", "the", "way", ",", "to", "navigate", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "What have you learned about yourself through that process?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "learned", "about", "yourself", "through", "that", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Well, fame can be a trap.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "fame", "can", "be", "a", "trap", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Seventeenth of September, you'll have -- presumably your brother and sister will be there, will they?", "question_tokens": ["Seventeenth", "of", "September", ",", "you", "'ll", "have", "--", "presumably", "your", "brother", "and", "sister", "will", "be", "there", ",", "will", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110831pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "If Floyd's watching, what's your message for him?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Floyd", "'s", "watching", ",", "what", "'s", "your", "message", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "I am taking my title home.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "taking", "my", "title", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]